

AYE CHAN MYAT

Senior Digital Marketing Executive

CONTACT

+959422856820

🗹 aye76863@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/aye-chanmyat-6948811b6

WORK EXPERIENCE

DIGITAL MARKETING EXECUTIVE

Jan 2021 - present

- Collaborated with project managers, designer and content writer related in social media.

Create FB Campaigns & Email Marketing, SMS Marketing, Viber Marketing

Design concept development and implementation for the main product application

- Leading a team of five mid-level designers
- Creating and editing graphic design assets for social media
- Coordinating social media teams and manager
- Design concept development and implementation for the main product application

Create flows and automations for FB and Messenger, Link sales process flows from Messenger and Shopify

Create Monthly Schedule for social media platform

WEB DESIGNER INTERN

Galaxy AI | Nov 2020 - Dec 2020

- Collaborated with project managers, testers, end-users, and distributors.
- Troubleshot and debugged code ensuring compatibility with devices, browsers, and operating systems.
- Developing and editing social media templates Developed user interfaces with modern JavaScript frameworks, HTML5 and CSS3.
- Working on the usability, development and implementation for Prototype

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF INFOMATION TECHNOLOGY (WYTU)

BE_IT | 2015 - 2020

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a Digital Marketing with 2 years experience and 1 year with graphic design and UX design. I am also experienced in coordinating a team of mid-level designers.quickly. As an extra talent, I can speak and write English Intermediate level.

EXPERTISE

Digital Marketing Tools Graphics Design UX Design Branding

SOFTWARE KNOWLEDGE

Canva

Photoshop

Shopify

Microsoft

Email,Google Sheet,Excel,PowerPoint,Word

PERSONAL SKILLS

Creativity

Team building

Communication

Problem Solving

Leadership

thank you!